{
    "id": "2d1afe8e9cea44c49bb8a8c2f38e04d7",
    "title": "Have and do",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6a505387376e43078c843e63e3bb186d",
            "title": "Have And Do Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………….. you known him for long?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Have",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................... she speak English?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where could they ……………….. gone?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. he be able to do this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Would",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. you manage to find him?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. she say anything?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went there but I ………………. not see anyone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………. not know what he is doing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………. never been to Australia.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………… not get along with her neighbors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}